My name is Bryan Mey. I'm the president of the Friends of Lums Pond.
I initially joined about five years ago.
Quickly fell in love with the volunteer work and have just been kind of diving headfirst into
trying to help out the park as much as I can.
It's hard to describe how far we've come.
We've done so much stuff from trail cleanups to member socials.
As big as like now we've got our big annual fundraiser that we call Pond Fest right over
there in Area 1.
Huge success the first two years.
We had 1,500 people show up last year, which was amazing.
Raised about $18,000, which is just phenomenal.
The community has been amazing.
And that's been what our efforts have been really is trying to channel the community.
A lot of people love this park and we're just trying to be the bridge that connects the community
to the park.
What 75 years means to me is that we've successfully created a protection of this beautiful nature
that we all love across Delaware.
And we just need to keep protecting it and keep putting things in place that help us sustain
and maintain the beauty that is Delaware State Parks.